[{"answer": " So, football season is going to start soon.  Things are going to get busy", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " What do you mean", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 14, "question": " So, football season is going to start soon.  Things are going to get busy", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  I forgot you havent been here in town for a football season yet", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 15, "question": " What do you mean", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " No, I havent.  What happens", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Oh, yeah.  I forgot you havent been here in town for a football season yet", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Things get a little out of hand.  No, Im only kidding.  Its not so bad", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 17, "question": " No, I havent.  What happens", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " I dont understand", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Things get a little out of hand.  No, Im only kidding.  Its not so bad", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Well, every other weekend there is a home game on campus.  When thi", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 19, "question": " I dont understand", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 23, "question": " Well, every other weekend there is a home game on campus.  When thi", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Yep.  You cant drive anywhere because the traffic is so bad.  There are s", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " Why red and black", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Yep.  You cant drive anywhere because the traffic is so bad.  There are s", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Those are the colors of the UGA football team and the university", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 32, "question": " Why red and black", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  I forgot.  I have noticed those colors everywhere in town", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 33, "question": " Those are the colors of the UGA football team and the university", "qSentId": 32},{"answer": " Dont worry.  On game day its really busy and lots of people are out shoutin", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 34, "question": " Oh, yeah.  I forgot.  I have noticed those colors everywhere in town", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " In the morning?  Why", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Dont worry.  On game day its really busy and lots of people are out shoutin", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " People start tailgating pretty early in the mornings before football games", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 39, "question": " In the morning?  Why", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Tailgating?  Whats that", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 40, "question": " People start tailgating pretty early in the mornings before football games", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Youve never heard of it", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Tailgating?  Whats that", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " No", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Youve never heard of it", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " OK.  Before the game, people cook out and eat and drink together, usually i", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 43, "question": " No", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " You mean outside", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 47, "question": " OK.  Before the game, people cook out and eat and drink together, usually i", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Yeah.  The part at the end of a truck is called a tailgate.  Lots of peopl", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 48, "question": " You mean outside", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " So they sit in the backs of their trucks and eat and drink", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Yeah.  The part at the end of a truck is called a tailgate.  Lots of peopl", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Yep.  Or they stand around their cars and do it", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 54, "question": " So they sit in the backs of their trucks and eat and drink", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " But why?  Why dont they go to a restaurant", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Yep.  Or they stand around their cars and do it", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " You know, I dont know.  Its just tradition, I guess.  I dont know what th", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 56, "question": " But why?  Why dont they go to a restaurant", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Strange, but I guess youre right", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 61, "question": " You know, I dont know.  Its just tradition, I guess.  I dont know what th", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Yeah, youll probably find lots of things Americans do strange", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Strange, but I guess youre right", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Do you like to go tailgating", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 66, "question": " Yeah, youll probably find lots of things Americans do strange", "qSentId": 65},{"answer": " Not really.  But I do like going to the games sometimes.  Have you ever bee", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 67, "question": " Do you like to go tailgating", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " No, never", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Not really.  But I do like going to the games sometimes.  Have you ever bee", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " Well, Ill have to take you to one and well go tailgating too.  Its just part of th", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 72, "question": " No, never", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Sure.  Im willing to try it.  It sounds kind of fun, actually", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Well, Ill have to take you to one and well go tailgating too.  Its just part of th", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": " It is fun.  People around here are football crazy and its pretty entertaining t", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 77, "question": " Sure.  Im willing to try it.  It sounds kind of fun, actually", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Do all students go to the games", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 79, "question": " It is fun.  People around here are football crazy and its pretty entertaining t", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " No, not all students.  But almost one-hundred thousand people go to eac", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Do all students go to the games", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Wow.  Thats a lot", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 86, "question": " No, not all students.  But almost one-hundred thousand people go to eac", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " Yeah.  Football is just a part of everyday life.  Even if you dont go to th", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Wow.  Thats a lot", "qSentId": 86},{"answer": " Im really happy that Im learning more about American life and that Ill get t", "docId": "08-01", "aSentId": 92, "question": " Yeah.  Football is just a part of everyday life.  Even if you dont go to th", "qSentId": 91}]
